we've been asked
to append 11 to the end of our array
and prepend 0 to the beginning
so let's just begin with appending 11 to
the end of our array
now there's more than one way that we
could do this
one is by calling the push method
we simply need to pass in the value that
we want to append
onto our array on line five i'm going
to output our array with p
and you'll see that this method is
destructive
now we see 11 at the end of our array
another way to achieve this is to append
with what we call the shovel operator
however this is an array method
this is also a destructive method
and again i'll output the array on line
five
and we see the output is the same
so next we want to prepend 0 to the
beginning of our array
to prepend a value to the beginning of
an array we call the
unshift method
and similarly to when we used the push
method
we simply want to pass in the value that
we want to add to our array
however this unshift method is
prepending the value onto the front of
the array
whereas the push method was appending it
onto the end of the array
this method is also destructive so now
on line 7 when we output our array
we expect to see 0 as the first element
in our array
and 11 as the last element
and that's what we see
you